Here
sil guys welcome back to Begusarai talking to the
fans of Bhula that you
get the benefit of this feature, no
one but to disable it the day after tomorrow, every detail
without going to Rudrapur, at this time the
company is telling you to be happy, guys please do
watch this pending so that you can get the
benefit, so before moving ahead in this video, take the
name, I will leave and
you are seeing the text invented in the morning, simply I will give
you a screenshot on the side,
please pay attention, so guys, simply
open the application, in a few seconds the
office opens, simply you have to
click on it in the left corner,
simply you can see here in the last you
can see the insurance new option
is available, click on it, when you click on it,
here you
get two options, Explorer, one
you will get policy, if you have added any policy,
any insurance, then
you will be taken to the My Policy section,
here you see, in the present
you have three category options available,
first daily  I used to sleep at night, it is the parental side
and friends, point station side, quiling ball
apps, so before this I have made a video on
speed and allied insurance from Devi Rate, main details,
if you
want details, speed will be given in the link description,
you can watch the video,
in the beginning of today, to tell you all, on the
notification light,
you have to click on withdrawal for complete details,
you can see here, then only and
only continue piece, you will have to
select the
features as per the right to enable the insurance, first of all let me
tell you, depression of image up to 1000 PM
prospective is required, if you
sleep on the domestic level website, then you
can avail the instant benefit, that is, if there is
any item during your trip, that means
if you feel or there is any item,
it can be planned till the tendency of shift, you should
Belgiri at home and
office, you can cover electric insurance,
friends, benefit and many more
questions, accident happens, this
₹1500000 If you can click on medical
equation then you can do it up to 2004,
hospitalization is to engine,
you can do collector institute here, that
means you can do emergency finance
and hotels, if you have Clinton then you can do
15000 km, then friends, you get Delhi tax
options, it is available according to this classification
Twenty20 per day,
friends, some of its features, as I
tell you, will be automatically edited if
you have enabled it, friends, let me
tell you, their retirement is to be provided by this, it is done by
such general insurance
company, you
can talk to Reliance customer support and
can do equations, there is a call reference, so here you will find
an option Get Help Worker, simple you have to
click on it, by clicking on it
you can see that
all the options are available in this post, you have to enable them,
simple you have to tap on it 100
percent Vipin
You will receive a call on your registered mobile number within 5 minutes. As soon as it is possible to get it, I have
given you complete details about insurance through solar light
and what about depression,
how much quit you get by combining its features,
then if you have
any question regarding insurance, then what kind of
support do you want to talk to them, so guys, if
you like the video, if you get success from this video, then guys
please
like this video and subscribe to your certified channel, so guys, we will
meet again
in the next video, till then bye take
care, thanks for watching, thank you.